We'll come back.
As I said before, the next few videos are
gonna be very, very important.
They talk about understanding
and gathering the requirements.
And this is super important
because if the interviewer gets
a doubt whether you are really worked
or not, he'll ask you about the
different roles and responsibilities.
Not just the interviewer, but also the recruiter will ask
you what the roles and responsibilities,
because they wanna screen you out whether you have really
worked or not, whether you're a genuine candidate or not.
So make sure you go through the next few videos
and really assimilate them.
Take down your notes and don't just skim through them, okay?
Write down notes in your own words.
And when ask you to write the share the
notes, do share them.
Okay? But the next immediate video
after this one is from a diamond membership course.
Okay? Now, in that video, I've talked about how
to even build a project from scratch.
'cause this project we're building now was built with help
of ai and I have explained how you can really
go about building your own project.
Okay? And I talked about different concepts over there, such
as Apache Park and Lake House,
and uh, CICD, which you may not know right now,
which is absolutely fine.
Nevertheless, the next video will definitely be I opener
for you about how, I mean in terms of how you can really
work on building a project from scratch for your portfolio.
And it'll also kind of help you in not just getting a
portfolio, but also in getting you the confidence,
of course, if you take the steps, if you take the steps in
getting you the confidence on not only cracking interview,
but also working in industry.
So the next video is very important.
Don't skip that,
but be mindful of the fact that
that video is on a diamond membership course.
And it talks about some concepts, which you don't know about
that yet, which is absolutely fine.
And as I said before, diamond membership is
currently closed right now.
And if you do wanna upgrade, you can join the wait list.
The link is in the video below.
So fill the form to join the wait list.
And again, this entire section is extremely important.
Do not skip any video. Go through every minute of it.